[Theme song]
[Meaningful music]
Shoot first
(Interpol police)
Vincenzo Cassano!
[The door bursts open]
[Italian]
It's Interpol
arrest you and
I came here to repatriate you to my home country.
(Police 1)
[Korean]
Throw away your gun
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano
[gunshot]
[Music that heightens the mood]
[shaking breathing]
Oh, don't come, don't come!
Don't come, don't come, don't come
[Hanseo’s trembling breathing]
[nervous music]
[Gun clangs]
[Rough breathing]
[shaking breathing]
[Italian]
Everybody put down your guns
[gunshot]
(Vincenzo)
[Korean]
Inyong Kim?
[Policeman 2’s trembling breathing]
Baek Kyung-soo?
(Police 1)
yes
Go tell your boss
Because it is impossible to prove the charges against me.
Interpol just went back
(Vincenzo)
and
Dispose of these bodies, okay?
(Police 2)
yes
If you don't follow my words
you die within two days
Baek Kyung-soo, do you understand?
(Police 1)
yes
Tsk
And you go back and tell it too
Please don't do this
Wait for me to die
Yes, I understand, yes
[shaking breathing]
Let's go, let's go
(Vincenzo)
Oh, I can't just let it go
You too, an appetizer
[gunshot]
[groans with difficulty]
(Chinese book)
I really thought I was going to die at that moment
[sigh]
(Seunghyuk)
For me, Interpol
They say Vincenzo will be caught easily.
You said you only do it for enticement, right?
Yes, I did.
Where did you get the gun again?
(Chinese book)
Oh, that's it
To kill Vincenzo
I bought a bag
(Myunghee)
The district prosecutor got Interpol involved.
Why did you bother to kill him?
Attorney Choi, are you an idiot?
(Chinese book)
Vincenzo is a mafia, mafia
If you go and don't get sentenced to death
I'll definitely come back again
They're going to kill us, right? huh?
Totally stupid
[Hanseo groans in pain]
(Junwoo)
on the ice rink
Were there Vincenzo’s men too?
(Chinese book)
yes
[Meaningful music]
Five people hid it.
What a bastard.
So, you were completely defeated in the end?
Although I am angry
Yes, brother
Did you know that Interpol was coming to arrest you?
When I see you hiding your subordinates
Oh, that's
I don't know either
[takes a breath]
Did you increase your subordinates according to the Mafia’s habit?
yes, maybe, yes
(Chinese book)
It seems so
If you don't want to die
Don't go around shooting carelessly.
(Junwoo)
Let's go, Choi Byeon.
(Chinese book)
Let’s go, Choi Byeon
Because you are busy
Please don't come to visit, yeah
[The door swings open]
[sigh]
[The door swings shut]
[groans with difficulty]
Chairman, what do you have?
Ah, there is something there.
There are bullet marks
You have to be honest with me.
Ugh, why is this happening between us?
Please just hold my hand, it hurts so much
[sigh]
(Chinese book)
Ah, ah, so much
I'll contact you later
(Chinese book)
Hey, where are you going?
(Myunghee)
As soon as he became the chief prosecutor
[Seunghyuk’s surprised groan]
Is this all you've done?
[Embarrassed laughter]
Well, work is
Well, there are times when I do well.
There are times when I fail and that's it.
How can it be easy if you try it yourself?
Well, just try it one more time
I think I'll master it
Do you know what the biggest thing is right now?
[Meaningful music]
(Seunghyuk)
I don't know
(Myunghee)
Our district prosecutor also
At the end of Vincenzo's killing department
I mean, you just put your name up a little bit.
If only I had stayed still
All of this would have been intact.
He said he called Interpol once.
It's up to the level of a murder department...
Don’t dance the Gae dance, which you’re not good at.
preserve our place
(Myunghee)
Let’s do our best to preserve this life.
A little dirty, huh?
Tsk, aig.
What now, I started talking politely, then I spoke informally, and then I stopped talking.
It went like this and then that and back and forth.
Just…
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, I am the head of the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office.
I don't buy it
(Chayoung and Joosung)
salty
[Vincenzo and Chayoung’s refreshing moans]
Oh my
If something is wrong, our lawyer now.
I'm not on a plane.
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
Oh my, it's dizzying just imagining it.
(Joosung)
Today I really said goodbye
Didn't you almost do it?
[Laughs slightly]
[Interesting music]
(Chinese book)
I have something urgent to discuss now.
Seunghyuk Han dragged Interpol into it.
I'm trying to take you to Italy.
They say they will arrive in Incheon in a little while.
[Tearing off hockey equipment]
[sigh]
Why are you scared?
Oh, of course
There must be more than one person with a gun.
Anyone just needs to come close to me
I'll take care of it after that.
[Machine operating sound]
(Joosung)
It's done
- That's nice.
- (Joosung) Yes
[dark music]
(Interpol police)
[Italian]
So
Are you saying Paolo was framed?
yes
(Interpol police)
how do you do that
Can we be sure?
If my priority was to run away
I would have killed you all
leave me behind
I'll give you a gift instead
[The whistle blows]
[Approaching footsteps]
[sigh]
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
Paolo gave to lawmakers and ministers
Bribery list and transcript!
[Korean]
And another one
Go to Malta tomorrow
Jason Fund
Find a shell company
And the accounting records and
Please conduct a joint investigation.
You will all be promoted to level 1.
(Vincenzo)
Is it heavy?
(Chinese book)
No, no, no
- (Vincenzo) I’ll carry it, it’s okay.
- (Hanseo) No, it’s okay, no.
- (Vincenzo) No...
- (Hanseo) Am I okay too?
(Vincenzo and Hanseo)
- You're having a hard time. Well, I'll lift it.
- Oh, no, it's not hard, it's not hard.
(Vincenzo)
No, they said they would make me the chairman.
Why didn't you betray me?
(Chinese book)
Hey, even if I became president
Doing it completely, is that?
It's just a marionette
So I just said I wouldn't do it.
(Vincenzo)
Good job, let's go
(Chinese book)
Uh, just a moment, just a moment, me
Because if I just go, it’s too obvious.
There are a lot of people living here, here, here
Shoot me gently so that only one shot passes by.
- (Vincenzo) Here on your arm?
- Yes
[laughter]
[Interesting music]
(Vincenzo)
What are you doing, gun?
(Chinese book)
Ah, the gun is here, ah
[Hanseo rustles his bag]
[breathes and then exhales]
- (Vincenzo) Silencer
- (Hanseo) Silencer?
- (Vincenzo) Quickly, quickly
- (Chinese) Quickly, quickly
[Hanseo’s nervous breathing]
[takes a breath]
But this
It hurts more than I thought, to the point where I fainted.
Hey, it's okay, pistol.
I can bear it
[Loads the gun]
[Hanseo moans in surprise]
(Vincenzo)
I didn't shoot
Shoot for three
three
- (Vincenzo) One, two
- (Chinese book) One, two
[gunshot]
[Hanseo’s scream]
[groans with difficulty]
[Vincenzo’s puzzled groan]
(Chinese book)
[in a difficult voice]
Wow, more than I thought...
It's okay, it's okay, Grandma.
Grandma, Grandma, why did you come?
[Hanseo falls down]
[Interesting music]
[Chuckling]
[Laughs slightly]
[laughter]
[Moaning in pain]
[Refreshing moan]
(Seokdo)
hey bin
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
[Seokdo’s Elasticity]
The morning sun is nice
- Shall we talk?
- (Vincenzo) Do you want to enjoy a sunny day?
Boy, I really
IC
Well…
(Seokdo)
What, Jasmine? coffee? A round ball? what?
That's enough
Do you have anything to say?
[Seokdo’s sigh]
(Seokdo)
It's nothing else
A new hot air balloon has arrived in Busan.
Completely new
Performance is very good
The distance flies so far away
But why are you telling me that?
Tsk
[Interesting music]
(Seokdo)
Ah, this
Well, if you keep doing difficult things,
A situation arises where you suddenly have to leave.
Then, when are you going to buy a plane ticket?
If you stop leaving the country
I can't even go out
(Vincenzo)
So
Ride this thing and run away?
47 people have already left this country safely.
(Seokdo)
Of course, unfortunately, two people became stars.
Well, you can trust the odds.
But you
Even though you did that to me
Why are you helping me?
Ah, this
Write, that…
Should I say it’s a romance?
[Lonely music]
[Seokdo’s sigh]
Like Michael Corleone in 'The Godfather'
There was a man who dreamed of life
But I actually met Corleone.
Bread!
It's respect, right?
[Slight moan]
Tsk, bitter
Well, I'll keep it for now.
[sigh]
hey bin
uh
brother
Can't you just call me that once?
[Welcome sigh]
You're saying the same thing
[humorous music]
To get hit, tsk
Yeah, whatever.
[Embarrassed laughter]
Wow, chicken skin is rising, all over my body.
Ah, suddenly, Mr. bitter
[Exciting music]
(Chayoung)
Number 1
Hanseok Jang Removing the pieces on the chessboard
I have to complete it
(Joosung)
Because all the words from Sangcheon-gu have been eliminated.
It seems like only big words are left now.
Write, then the big words
Let's deal with it today, okay?
(Chayoung)
Our big words today
You must be in a lot of trouble.
(Vincenzo)
Manager, what about the Babel Tower lawsuit?
I'm ready
Oh, just take it to court.
[Laughs slightly]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Video sound plays]
[Exciting music]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Junwoo)
Go to Glory Cheongeum Cafe until 3 p.m.
If you don't come, I'll hold you responsible.
Chairman Jang Han-seok
[sigh]
[Elegant music plays]
[Director Tae’s sigh]
(Director Tae)
Hey, well, let’s meet somewhere like this.
Are you saying that now?
That's right
Ah, in an open space like this
What are we going to do now?
(Director Cheon)
You don’t know how surprised I was when I received the text message.
(Director Tae)
In that way without being rude
Sending a message
Tsk
[Speaker beeps]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang in the recording)
Oh, are you really going to Babel Tower?
[Director Tae’s embarrassed groan]
[Exciting music]
From what I hear
What, you said there was going to be a reinvestigation?
(Director Tae in the recording)
In my experience...
(Director Tae)
No, this sound
Why is it coming out here, this, huh?
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Hey, what are you doing?
I need to turn that thing off quickly.
Turn that thing off quickly, quickly!
(Director Cheon)
Who is the boss here, boss!
[Miri’s urgent breathing]
(in advance)
What's going on?
(Director Tae and Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
- Turn off that sound, this sound, please.
- Turn it off quickly, turn it off quickly, turn it off quickly.
(in advance)
Oh, yes, I understand.
(Hanseo in the recording)
This is just trivial
It's a document error issue.
[The volume increases]
It's not a big deal
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Hey, hey, hey, hey, it's bigger!
Where's the code, code
[Myunghee speaks in the recording]
code, code, code
(Myunghee in the recording)
don't worry
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Ana, child, me
[Chief Prosecutor Hwang sighs]
Oh my
(in advance)
sorry
[Director Cheon clears his throat]
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Chairman Jang
Baby, are you really going to do it this way?
(Junwoo)
I don't know much either.
Ah!
Not anywhere else
It was recorded at Chairman Jang’s house.
At home!
[Exciting music]
Ha, then it could be wiretapping...
(Chief Prosecutor Hwang)
Now, when Director Seo died.
The situation is completely different
I'm not alone
If it keeps coming out like this
I really don't stay still, okay?
Chief Prosecutor
[Call end sound]
Mistress
I'm going to turn around, really.
[Camera shutter sounds repeatedly]
(Chayoung)
This time
All negativity related to the Tower of Babel
We plan to uproot it.
Perhaps a shocking truth
You will witness it
(Reporter 1)
The person next to you
I just want to ask you one thing.
The Tower of Babel in the Bible
It collapses because of human desires.
(Vincenzo)
in this court
It will be recreated exactly as it appears in the Bible.
The barbell will fall before it goes up.
(Reporter 2)
Please tell me one word of your determination.
[Chayoung sighs]
Our last words to Babel
This will be it
It doesn't go far
camera zoom
[Emphasized sound effect]
[Italian]
Goodbye!
[Music that heightens the mood]
(Reporter 3)
[Korean]
I would like to ask you one more question.
[Reporters are noisy]
(Heesu)
Wow
[Heesu’s laughter]
Please eat some fruit
(dropping)
Oh my, I'm sorry.
I'm on my way to go out for alms.
[Chae-shin laughs slightly]
ah…
You often go out for alms these days.
[Heesu’s laughter]
It seems like you've been going out every day for the past few days.
Are you having a hard time taking care of me?
(Chae Shin)
Oh no, no
(dropping)
Please leave the fruit inside.
I will eat well
- Yes
- (Dropping) Okay then.
[Heesu’s laughter]
(Heesu)
Come back
[Calm music]
[sigh]
Only when believers come will life flourish.
[Heesu’s sigh]
What should I do, um
[Cheolwook sighs]
(Cheolwook)
If you go out for alms every day like that,
This situation seems to be very bad.
(Heesu)
Yeah
[Yeonjin sighs]
(Yeonjin)
Is there money saved by monks?
What could there be?
[Heesu’s sigh]
(Heesu)
No, the shopping mall looks like this.
Which believer will come?
I don’t want to go either, but I’m a Christian.
Then let’s go to 10 o’clock general
Let's help the monks
Okay, okay?
Even if it's difficult, we have to share it with each other.
Hey, I also spoke to the laundromat owner.
I'll talk to you
[Yeonjin responds]
(Cheolwook)
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah, uh, gone, gone
(Vincenzo)
Because I filed a complaint
A tilted playground
Shall we correct this?
(Chayoung)
Yes, just like my father wanted.
We have to start harshly and harshly.
I'm doing it gently
The lawyer is really cool.
See you later
(Chinese book)
Uh, okay
[Call end sound]
The wiretapping device was inspected and it is clean.
[takes a breath]
How on earth do you record...
(Myunghee)
Weren’t there many people gathered?
It's likely you're one of them
No, it was Vincenzo's doing.
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
A shame worse than death
To give you this I
Starting today, I will play chess with you.
and hear your words
I will destroy them one by one
[laughter]
Bishop, Knight, Rook
It seems like everything has flown away
If what Vincenzo did is right
It seems like a big hit this time
(Chinese book)
Oh my, humans are so light
Backless old guys
So then
When I said let's blow it up
If you blow it up, that's fine, nothing like this will happen.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Anyway, you didn't listen to me
What, why, what happened?
Hong Cha-young against Babel Group
I filed a lawsuit for damages.
[Meaningful music]
Was the suit checkmated?
[sigh]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Yes, this is Chief Prosecutor Han Seung-hyuk.
[Music that heightens the mood]
(Vincenzo)
Interpol sent me off well.
I just followed the legal procedures.
It would be difficult if it was like that.
The word legal
How could it be this awkward?
This is what the current district prosecutor says.
Let's negotiate tonight
Well, why am I with you?
Should I negotiate?
If you want to live, come out
I hang up on three, one, two
[Call end sound]
I hate it, Mr.
I hung up
Ah, it was taken away again, this, Icy.
Oh, this one again
What are we talking about, tsk
[Atmospheric music plays]
[Myunghee clinks the ice]
Can I get some wet towels?
I'll join you for a moment.
(Myunghee)
It's coming to me well
Are you my sasaeng fan?
Although it has not been decided
The person who accepted me when I was leaving
You look very comfortable.
(Myunghee)
Yeah
We can kill Neg first.
Have you ever thought about it?
Yeah, not at all
Instead, the Babel Tower lawsuit
If the lawyer wins
I'll extend your life
That's it
The dream of extending life
I'll go to the convenience store and make it happen
(Myunghee)
I forgot some yogurt
[Elasticity]
(Chayoung)
But
Even if you live, you're not living, right?
Because
[makes a loud noise]
Because I'm going to send it away again
[laughter]
[Chayoung hums]
[Meaningful music]
(Hwanggyu in the recording)
Me and my subordinate Pyo Hyuk-pil
Under the instigation of lawyer Choi Myeong-hee
Attorney Hong Yoo-chan
He faked his death in a car accident.
(Myunghee)
Oh my, our poor little beads, huh?
There are 100 days of records like that.
(Hwanggyu in the recording)
In this way, Attorney Choi Myung-hee's
People who received orders and processed them
Rep. Baek Min-woo
Park Dong-cheon, Chief of Information Division, Gudam Police Station
Assistant Minister Jeong Jin-taek
Seonwoo Lee, Chairman of the Proper Politics Coalition
Reporter Lee Yang-soo of Sunwoo Ilbo
[Puts down the fork]
Minhyuk Kim, Chairman of TQ Logistics Union
(Myunghee)
It's useless for nothing
What should we do with the names?
This is my Christmas present this year
I'll definitely give it to you
About 30 years in prison?
You are now a dog with poop on it, a dog with bran on it
Don’t you think something is going on?
Who poops?
Oh, the lawyer is shit?
Me?
Vincenzo or you
(Myunghee)
Well, if you pounce on us
Do you think it will look clean?
I don't want to look clean
You want to be a stronger piece of shit.
(Myunghee)
[Snaps fingers]
yes
That's it!
good words
Who is the really strong shit?
Let's try it till the end
[Chayoung clears her throat]
[Refreshing moan]
[takes a breath]
[Sighing]
Yeah, whatever.
(Seunghyuk)
Tsk, this and that
I know it hurt your feelings, but
When it comes to war,
Collateral damage occurs.
Collateral damage, something like that
[Seunghyuk’s laughter]
By the way
What do you mean by negotiating?
[laughter]
(Vincenzo)
Huh?
[Puts down chopsticks]
[laughter]
(Seunghyuk)
Thank you
[Pouring a drink]
negotiating for your life
what?
Originally, I was going to save him.
[Meaningful music]
[Puts the kettle down]
Because you're playing with Interpol
I decided to kill again
[laughter]
Ah, what is this?
That's not up for negotiation
[laughter]
Life is given to existence
Isn't it the best gift?
hey!
(Seunghyuk)
I'm the chief prosecutor of the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office, huh?
Where is the little guy's bastard?
Playing pranks on adults, Mr.
[laughter]
Don't talk about your age
[Pours a drink]
Age is not a matter of rank, but of responsibility.
Don't speak informally, you bastard!
uh? 계속 반말
이 새끼가 그냥, 쯧
(승혁)
반말하지 마, 인마! Tsk
[Thumping the table]
But man!
I told you to come in, I told you to come in
If I hit this, I’ll come in…
[The door clicks open]
(Man 1)
The CEO has to say ‘hey’ in order for us to…
[heavy music]
(Seunghyuk)
Ugh, Mr.
[sigh]
My palms are killing me, Mr.
It's older and more childish than I thought.
It's the biggest disappointment in a while
The original fight
It's old and childish.
You know very well
[sigh]
[Meaningful sound effects]
[gunshot]
[Men's screams]
[Interesting music]
[Seunghyuk’s surprised groan]
Well, there will be no need to remove the bullet through it.
What, what, what are you doing
Quick, quick, quick, quick!
Do something, quickly!
Gun, no gun, gun?
Everyone go out
[Men's groans of difficulty]
Everyone get out!
(Seunghyuk)
Get out there, that, that, that
Take out everything that's stuck
[Men's groans of difficulty]
[The door slams shut]
[Seunghyuk’s surprised groan]
[shaking breathing]
For a cunning human being
No one had guts
That's right, that's right, I'm very cunning.
(Seunghyuk)
sorry
[Crying]
Please save me
[Door sound is heard]
[nervous music]
(Junwoo)
What is it, Mr. Lee?
(Ghost)
It's a punishment for being careless with the elderly.
[laughter]
[The spirit of the monster]
(Junwoo)
Ai!
[Fight noisily]
[A dog barks in the distance]
[Junwoo’s urgent groan]
[Junwoo’s heavy breathing]
[car horn]
[Rough breathing]
[sigh]
[Moaning in pain]
[Junwoo groans in pain]
[groans with difficulty]
[Junwoo’s groans with difficulty]
Geez, oldies, huh?
How dare you, my brother? Are you targeting your brother?
[mumbling]
(Myunghee)
Elderly people are very
You are full-blooded.
After all these provocations
(Chinese book)
Ah, the soles of my feet.
[Meaningful music]
Well, just, just
Should I just blow it up, just, eh?
Still in Korea
These guys are using their strength.
If you touch it incorrectly, it will swell.
Even if not now
I have to deal with it all someday
These are useless words now
[dark music]
[A siren rings in the distance]
[Italian]
the devil
torment the devil
[laughter]
[Urgent music]
(Man 2)
[Korean]
Stand there!
[Man 2’s powerful moans]
[President Cho’s groans of difficulty]
[Fight noisily]
(Man 3)
catch
(Man 4)
let's go
[President Cho’s groans of difficulty]
(Director Kim)
Ah, just be gentle, tsk.
[Director Kim’s powerful moans]
[Meaningful music]
Do you know who I am?
Director Kim
Prosecutor Jeong In-guk and I from the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
(Director Kim)
We've been close friends for a long time.
[Putting down the bottle]
Geom Jeong said that
To open the secret room door of Geumga Plaza
Find yourself first
[laughter]
I can't open it
Eye data is behind closed doors
(Director Kim)
Then we'll have to find another way, okay?
Who is the vault security designer?
I don't know
From President Wang’s side
I understand that you were invited.
(Director Kim)
Usually in other countries
When creating a security system
Why do you use someone from that country?
Each country has a security system or
Because the method is different
Now
[sigh]
(Director Kim)
Starting today, you will be with my subordinates.
I have work to do
Active in Korea during that period
top security experts
and hackers
Investigate everything
[laughter]
How did you do all that...
(Director Kim)
You are an informant.
Make it happen, okay?
If you don't want to die with your family
(Junwoo)
Wow, Mr.
[Junwoo’s groans with difficulty]
[Oncoming car engine sound]
[Thai fricative sound]
(Junwoo)
What is that again?
[nervous music]
[The bodyguard's spirit]
[Fight noisily]
(Junwoo)
Hey, hey, hey, hey, let's go, let's go!
Hey, hey, let's go!
[gunshot]
[tire rubbing sound]
[Junwoo’s powerful moans]
[Junwoo’s heavy breathing]
[angry moaning]
[Rough breathing]
[Sighing]
This
I really can't leave it like this.
If this continues, President Jang will die.
To terrorism, to shootings
Just arrest Vincenzo and the elders.
(Seunghyuk)
No, if you know, why are you like this?
redemption?
That's when we're in control
It's possible
While doing something wrong
From bribery to guillotine files
It's all bad
No, the Chief Prosecutor of the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
That one mafia bastard
Can't you catch it?
No, the Southeastern District Prosecutor's Office of the world
From Ace
Well, isn’t there a single thing you’re trying to control?
(Myunghee)
Hey!
[surprised moan]
This is the southeastern district prosecutor’s office right now!
Lower your voice
Yes, yes, yes
[Clears cough]
(Seunghyuk)
Hey there
I did some deep thinking and
Let’s also use the mafia method.
Where is the safest place in this situation?
[Snaps fingers]
It's a prison cell.
You know? what am i saying
Don't talk nonsense.
It makes sense
(Seunghyuk)
Even Vincenzo Cassano
Breaking into the cell?
That's not easy
[Meaningful music]
What does that mean?
(Junwoo)
Are you telling me to go to jail?
It will take 1 or 2 weeks.
I will take all measures within.
(Junwoo)
Byun Choi
You know how much I hate prison cells
Because I don't want to go to jail
I've been living my life hiding my identity!
I know it well
(Myunghee)
I'm not really asking you to go in.
This is for protection
(Junwoo)
What about protection?
I really don't want to go in
Now you have to admit it
Vincenzo
It's too strong an opponent
Oh, really!
These are not empty words
(Junwoo)
I really don't want to go!
(Myunghee)
don't be afraid
I really have everything inside
We will decorate it like a hotel.
IC
[Junwoo sighs]
(Junwoo)
Ouch!
[Junwoo taps the window]
[Meaningful music]
[Junwoo sighs]
(Investigator)
Mr. Jang Han-seok
At the Special Tax Evasion Department of the Southeastern District Prosecutors' Office
came out
You are subject to certain economic aggravated punishment laws.
Arrested for tax evasion
Me?
(Investigator)
Oh, you
You have the right to appoint a lawyer
There is an opportunity to make excuses
Probation of arrest and detention
You have the right to file a claim in court
(Chinese book)
Hey, what is it?
They always arrest innocent people, huh?
(Junwoo)
Be quiet.
There are a lot of people
[The investigator rattles the handcuffs]
Just one minute before I go
Let me talk to my brother.
[Hanseo sighs]
Launch Babel Bio while I'm away
(Chinese book)
Oh, I put that on hold.
[Meaningful music]
What?
Suspicions about Babel Bio
It's very spread out
Well, inflating stocks?
It was established for the purpose of accounting manipulation.
Who wants you to make that kind of judgment?
(Chinese book)
No, no, it's not my judgment.
The judgment of our board of directors and planning office
This is for reference.
Hey
(Chinese book)
And brother
Like Elizabeth Holmes to me.
You told me to become a manager.
[Hanseo sighs]
But that woman is a fraud.
I'm in jail now
To me like that
What you're asking me to do is become a manager
Well, you're telling me to become a fraudster.
It can't be like that.
To be a burden to my brother
[laughter]
(Junwoo)
you
Do you really want to die? uh?
[Hanseo’s frightened breathing]
[Hanseo’s trembling breathing]
[laughter]
Lady, it's hard
Why die?
It's all for my brother
[Rhythmic music]
[laughter]
[Hanseo’s laughter]
[Hanseo claps his hands]
I'll take you with me
[laughter]
Who wants to go out to eat?
[sigh]
[nervous music]
Uh, uh, get out
[Junwoo’s elasticity]
[The door clicks open]
[The door clicks shut]
(Seunghyuk)
It's been a rough ride, Mr. Chairman.
[Junwoo clears his throat]
It’s been a while, Prosecutor Jeong.
Hello, Chairman.
It’s been a while for me too…
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laugh]
Vincenzo won't leave it alone.
Can I come back like this?
Weren't you threatened?
I was threatened once.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
However, the prosecutor of the Republic of Korea
You can't give in to the mafia.
(Seunghyuk)
Our Prosecutor Jeong will be the head of the department next week.
Yes, you will be stronger
[Meaningful music]
(Junwoo)
Then what
I'll be watching and looking forward to it.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
thank you
Thank you too
[Seunghyuk’s awkward laugh]
[Atmospheric music plays]
[Refreshing moan]
(Vincenzo)
Did you learn drinking etiquette well?
(Chinese book)
Ah, even though I lack knowledge
Well, I learned etiquette well.
Ah, hot, ah, hot
Write, I, but
You really won't kill me, right?
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
[Puts down the bottle]
[Sigh of relief]
You're like a reflection
I feel like I'm doing it
Yes, but how do you know?
Am I doing something similar to reflection?
It could all just be a pretense.
Reflection is not done with words
Maintaining the changed behavior
(Vincenzo)
Well, I don't know how long it will last
I think it's still holding up well
(Chinese book)
Uh, really…
How can you say this...
Do you do it coherently like this?
Praise, compliment, compliment
Because it's cool
[Embarrassed laughter]
But why did you turn down the position of chairman?
Are you helping me?
(Chinese book)
[Sighing]
Um…
Why are you helping?
Write
Um…
just something
Like a brother
[Hanseo puts down the bottle]
Ah, that's a little strange.
[Calm music]
It's easy to get criticized
It's comfortable to play hockey together
It's easy to have a drink like this
I heard so.
[Hanseo’s awkward laugh]
Oh, hey, I'm asking you a favor while you're drunk.
When I'm just like this
Can’t I just call him brother?
Uh, no.
Yes, Vincenzo Cassano.
Instead, don’t climb just because it’s comfortable.
Bin, Bin
(Chinese book)
[Laughing]
Binnie hyung
[Men are talking]
[dark music]
[sigh]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Junwoo’s angry groan]
Jang Han-seo, you bastard
(prison guard)
6723, visitation
[The door slams shut]
[The guard jingles his keys]
[The door clicks shut]
I'm glad I came back when I was bored
(Junwoo)
What do you think?
My prison uniform fits well, right?
(Vincenzo)
Yeah
You look like you're at a Cancun resort.
I really like it here
People are nice too
(Vincenzo)
You think you're safe in there, right?
Well, there will be some shoulders to protect you.
The detention warden will also treat you well.
Do you do this in Italy too?
You know because you've done it a lot.
I'm sorry for breaking the mood, but
All of this
Do you think everything is going according to plan?
[Meaningful music]
[tire rubbing sound]
[gunshot]
(Vincenzo)
That your car has bulletproof glass
Did he really not know?
[Junwoo’s heavy breathing]
[Junwoo chuckles]
(Vincenzo)
Those monsters back then
could really kill you
Do you think it wasn't there?
Sent Chairman Jang Han-seok to detention center
(Vincenzo)
So that you don't notice
Uh, I could put him in jail.
If I create a sin
Wouldn't it be too obvious?
A very natural environment tomorrow morning
It will be made
[Elasticity]
(Seunghyuk)
Ah, yes
(Vincenzo)
What locked you in there
It's me
[laughter]
Even though I lose every day
As much as the enemy can't analyze the loss
There's nothing to be happy about
Just kill it, you mafia bastard.
(Junwoo)
Don't bother me
To be honest
Why don't you kill me
Because you're afraid, right?
If you try to kill me, you're afraid of what happens next.
Isn't it?
[sigh]
Tsk
I thought you were smart
You still don't notice
[Meaningful music]
(Vincenzo)
This is my first time confessing
Do you know what my nickname is in the mafia world?
[Speaks Italian]
‘A full cat’ in Korean
A cat that is full
If you catch a mouse all day long
I play with it and then eat it.
When I was young, my first
A robber who killed his adoptive parents.
내가 마피아가 돼서
그 새끼를 2년 동안 괴롭혔어
근데 그 새끼가 자살 시도를 했네
난 그 새끼를 가장 좋은 병원에서
치료받게 해 주고 퇴원시켰어
그리고 퇴원한 그날
최고의 요리를 먹이고
바로 죽여 버렸지
내가 지금까지 널 살려 둔 진짜 이유는
쥐처럼 갖고 놀기 위해서야
[헛웃음]
이게 내 진짜 모습이거든
잡아먹기 전
마지막으로 갖고 노는 단계
네가 유리방 안에서
바벨타워가 무너지는 걸
보게 하는 거
나 내일이라도 나갈 수 있어
[헛웃음]
[긴장되는 음악]
(빈센조)
라구생 갤러리에 있던
네 페이퍼 컴퍼니 자료
정 검사한테
원본 파일 하나만 준 줄 알았어?
[Italian]
You idiot!
[Korean]
Oh my, Mr.
If this is evidence, you at least
I have to stay in there for another month.
Geom Jeong, Byeon Choi, no matter how these two
Even if we put our heads together and squeeze
[laughter]
Watch closely inside the glass room.
How the Tower of Babel Collapsed
[Music that heightens the mood]
[Junwoo’s angry groan]
[Rough breathing]
(prison guard)
6723, return
(Junwoo)
Let go!
[Seunghyuk sighs]
Ragusaeng Gallery Paper Company Materials
Vincenzo said there were no copies?
yes
It was like that back then
(Seunghyuk)
Hey, just talking about the mafia...
Oh, I'm really going crazy, Mr. Lee.
This is a criminal complaint.
It won't take more time
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Yes, Chairman Jang.
It seems difficult to leave right now.
If Chairman Jang does something wrong,
I'm really going to put a stake in here, huh?
Several elderly people
Isn’t that what you want?
(Seunghyuk)
Hey!
Is that so?
The guillotine file is
Chairman Jang Han-seo can find it.
[Meaningful music]
First, with Ragusaeng Gallery materials,
Let's tie it up a little more.
(Seunghyuk)
Is that so?
Yeah, well, by the way.
But I am this Babel Tower
I'm more worried about this, this lawsuit.
Vincenzo and Hong Cha-young
You never know what I might do
Chief Prosecutor
Please delay the appointment of the manager for a moment.
(Prosecutor Jeong)
Babel Tower lawsuit and Chairman Jang case
I will handle it myself.
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[Italian]
Luca!
(Luca)
Consiglieri
I have now arrived at Incheon Airport.
Incheon?
what's the matter?
[Korean]
I never thought Vincenzo would draw a picture like this.
I didn't know
sorry
[Junwoo claps his hand]
(Junwoo)
Well, anyway
It's safe, right?
yes
The paper company case is
Me and Prosecutor Jeong
I'll take care of it.
(Myunghee)
Babel Tower too
[Clears cough]
You can’t go out right now, right?
yes
[Meaningful music]
me here
I can’t see the Tower of Babel collapsing.
Get it out as quickly as possible, okay?
yes, i understand
Oh, and keep an eye on Hanseo.
Because I feel like I've lost my temper a lot these days.
(Kiseok)
[English]
Can I help you?
[Interesting music]
[Mobile phone operation sound]
[Guidance voice]
[Korean]
We are looking for Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
[Elasticity]
[Italian]
Consiglieri
yes
(Kiseok)
Please follow me
[Vincenzo pats Luca]
Luca, how are you?
(Joosung)
[Korean]
Uh, wait a minute.
[Interesting music]
Luca, Luca, Luca
(Kiseok)
Luca, Luca, Luca, Luca
[Laughing]
Luca
[Laugh together]
Welcome, Luca
(Luca)
[Italian]
Are you friends?
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
everyone likes you
[Kiseok’s laughter]
Luca
[Vincenzo’s happy exclamation]
[Patting together]
[Calm music]
(Luca)
Consiglieri
Dario and Sebastian
I was attacked by the Luciano family.
I don't know who will die today too
[Swearing in Italian]
(Vincenzo)
What is Paolo doing?
(Luca)
From the beginning, Paolo
wasn't interested
Information circulated that Paolo was being investigated.
to run away
Looks like I'm organizing my assets
[Angrily moaning]
Bad guy! A man without conscience!
(Joosung)
[Korean]
Something looks very serious, right?
(Kiseok)
Looks like some people died
I think Consiglieri swore.
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Luca)
[Italian]
Consiglieri
come back to italy
Please save my family
If it goes on like this
Our family is over
[sigh]
[Call connection tone]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
[President Cho sighs]
“Result: Success”
(President Cho)
[Korean]
The most influential security experts and hackers
It was shortened to 4 people.
see last chapter
[nervous music]
[Director Kim laughs]
(Director Kim)
Is your current address Geumga Plaza?
(President Cho)
yes
[Director Kim’s laughter]
Did the locksmith live next to the safe?
[Director Kim sighs]
[Vincenzo takes a breath and then exhales]
[sigh]
[Clicks open the lighter]
[Closes the lighter]
[Calm music]
“Vincenzo”
[Chayoung pours a drink]
[Puts down the bottle]
[Computer notification sound]
[Chayoung’s refreshing groan]
[Mouse operation sound]
[Laughing]
What is it
"Miss Benning
“I’m sending you a photo I took a few days ago.”
[Mouse operation sound]
"Photo of the Month"
"George Anderson & Jessica Bening
"Marriage proposal"
[Calm music]
[Vincenzo takes a breath and then exhales]
[Jusung sobs]
(Joosung)
[Sobbing]
don't go
Hehe, really
(Chayoung)
It's not like I'm going to a battlefield, just
(Joosung)
It's a battlefield, right?
Go and talk to other organizations
We might have to fight...
(Chayoung)
Write, drop
pop
That doesn't work
(Vincenzo)
Manager
I'll be back in just two weeks.
don't worry
It's a people thing
(Joosung)
2 weeks turned into 4 weeks, 4 weeks turned into 8 weeks
8 weeks...
[Clap your hands]
Just a little!
[sniffling]
(Chayoung)
He's a bit of an obnoxious character today.
Our office manager
sorry
It's okay
There won't be any major problems for the time being.
(Chayoung)
Chairman Jang is also in detention center.
Boy, really
Look at the expression
[Calm music]
They say Geumga Plaza is an iron fortress.
[laughter]
[Vincenzo’s sigh]
(Chayoung)
Oh my
Manager
Don't cry like a man
Wipe away your tears and come out
[Sobbing]
[sniffles]
[breathes and then exhales]
(Yeonjin)
uh? Sister, please come out quickly.
(Heesu)
Uh, uh, go
Hey there
Oh my
Hey, this is red pepper paste and dried radish.
[Calm music]
Make sure you eat well when you go, okay?
- (Vincenzo) Thank you
- (Heesu) Let’s put this here, okay.
(in advance)
This
This is my mom’s pickled godeulppaegi.
[Miri laughs slightly]
Ah…
(in advance)
I'll put this in too
(Yeonjin)
Ah, this brings good luck.
Be sure to take this with you
(Cheolwook)
Yes, it's real, this is
They say it's a spirit thing, yeah
[Yeonjin responds]
thank you
(Larry Kang)
We will take good care of you for two weeks.
(Toto)
Maybe
If you go, it doesn’t mean you can’t come back, right?
(Hongsik)
Oh my, why can't I come?
The main strategy is, tsk
(Kiseok)
Sort out the situation there.
He will come right away
(dropping)
Buddha will be with you every moment
wooden avalokitesvara bodhisattva
thank you
Have a nice trip
(Vincenzo)
Thanks, bro
[Miss Sobbing]
[Clears cough]
Have a nice trip
Let's go now
(Joosung)
passport
[Vincenzo laughs slightly]
(Larry Kang)
Please take care
(Heesu)
Well, I, I eat well.
(Yeonjin)
Come back quickly!
(in advance)
hello
- (Sunam) Why are you crying?
- (Yeonjin) Baby, why are you crying?
[Miss Sobbing]
(Joosung)
[Laughing]
Baby, come back soon, it’s 2 weeks, 2 weeks.
- (Heesu) Oh my gosh
- (Miss Miss) Is it true?
(Cheolwook)
Are you crying?
(Yeonjin)
I cried
- (Seokdo) Crying
- (Yeonjin) Oh, you cried, right?
[Joosung’s laughter]
(Vincenzo)
Come in
(Chayoung)
Let’s go to the arrival hall together.
(Vincenzo)
It's okay
I'll be back
In the meantime, I am preparing well for the lawsuit.
yes
Perfume, scarves, etc.
You never have to buy it, ever.
[Laughs]
[Soft music]
[Laugh together]
Come on in and have a cup of coffee.
If anything happens
Contact me right away
don't worry
I'll go
(Chayoung)
Luca
[sigh]
(Chayoung)
Lawyer!
[Heavy breathing]
[Italian]
What is a friend?
dwelling in two bodies
is one soul
[surprised elasticity]
[Calm music]
[Vincenzo’s laughter]
(Chayoung)
[Korean]
Because I’m hurting too
don't ever get hurt
I promise
(crew member)
Do you need wine?
It's okay
[Calm piano playing]
[Tense sound effect]
[Miri moans]
[nervous music]
[Miri’s labored moans]
(Director Kim)
hi
Seo Mi-ri, nice to meet you.
Because we're not friends
We don't need to know each other
open it quickly
Well, I don't know about this.
I don't know how to open it
[Miri’s labored moans]
[Director Kim sighs]
If I say I can't do it one more time
I'll kill you right away
[Laughs]
[The door clicks open]
[The door clicks shut]
[Joosung laughs slightly]
(Joosung)
Did you see them off well?
Sure
[Calm music]
(Chayoung)
Go and organize it well.
It's been like that here too.
yes
(Joosung)
But something happened and then he wasn't there.
I feel empty
[Joosung’s laughter]
What, two weeks?
[Joosung sets down his glass]
It will go by quickly, as we prepare for the lawsuit.
(Chayoung)
yes
Let's work hard to prepare for the lawsuit.
Fighting!
[laughter]
[Strong moan]
(Chayoung)
Fighting!
[Laugh together]
[Chayoung clears her throat]
[nervous music]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[Director Kim sighs]
[sigh]
[Keyboard operation sound]
[System operating sound]
[The safe door clicks open]
It's open
[sigh]
[Meaningful music]
[Director Kim sighs]
(Director Kim)
Where are the gold bars and guillotine files?
I don't know
(Director Kim)
AC
Where did you steal it?
It's true, I really don't know.
[Director Kim’s powerful moans]
(Director Kim)
This bastard!
To be honest
Where did you steal it?
[Miri’s powerful moans]
[Man 5 screams]
(Director Kim)
Ana, Mr.
Oh, catch it.
[Men's spirit]
[Fight noisily]
(in advance)
Laundry owner!
Pawn shop owner!
Boss Seokdo!
[Sobbing]
(Chayoung)
Miri, what's going on?
(in advance)
Bad guys came to Nanyaksa Temple
(Chayoung)
Who are the bad guys?
[Miri sobs]
[Footsteps are heard]
[Joosung’s urgent groan]
[Miri’s frightened groan]
(Chayoung)
Manager, hurry up and go up.
Bring my family
No, it's dangerous with just the two of you.
Quick!
[Chayoung’s heavy breathing]
(Director Kim)
Mr. Seo Mi-ri
I come here when you say nice things
[nervous music]
(Chayoung)
Who are you?
(Director Kim)
Leave out the third party.
This is a dangerous situation
I'm not a third party, I'm a two-party lawyer.
Oh, straw?
Attorney Hong Yu-chan’s daughter?
How do you know my father?
(Director Kim)
Of course I know
He's an amazing person.
I just need to know
go quickly
(Director Kim)
Attorney Hong
I teach my daughter to be polite to adults.
Looks like they didn't teach you
To people like you
Because you taught me not to be polite
(Director Kim)
Bring it quickly
Get your hands off me!
I can never take you with me!
[Miri’s frightened groan]
[Chayoung and Miri’s surprised moans]
(Chayoung)
Don't do it!
[Miri’s scream]
[Man 6 groans in pain]
[There is a crunching sound]
[Chayoung and Miri’s surprised gasps]
[upbeat music]
[Man 6 groans in pain]
[There is a crunching sound]
[Italian]
Wait!
[Man 6 groans with difficulty]
[Man 6 screams]
[Man 6 falls]
(in advance)
[Korean]
Lawyer
Are you two okay?
Why didn't you go?
I solved it another way
(Vincenzo)
Oh, and
I forgot to feed Injagi.
[President Cho’s laughter]
[Laughs]
[President Cho sighs]
Anyway, I'm taking a step back.
Maybe Vincenzo Cassano?
Well, I don’t know anything about that.
Let's pay some price in 5 minutes.
[Director Kim sighs]
[Splendid music]
[Rhythmic music]
Subtitle: Kwon Jeong-won